you guys this looks like a fun one 99
factorial minus 98 factorial over 99
factorial plus 98 factorial would you
want to try this on your own pause it
because I'm going to solve it in three
two one a lot of calculators aren't
going to be able to handle these numbers
these are very large numbers but we
don't need a calculator we can solve it
by hand First Step let's rewrite this 99
factorial as 99 times 98 factorial and
let's subtract this and let's rewrite
this as 1 times 98 factorial and then
we're going to do the same thing on the
bottom except we're going to be adding
the two terms all of these terms have a
98 factorial so let's factor that out of
top and bottom if we do 98 factorial
times 99 it'll bring us back to this
right here and then we're going to
subtract 98 factorial times 1. and same
thing on bottom but it's going to be a
plus and then the 98 factorial on top
and bottom those can cancel each other
out so we're just left with 99 minus 1
which is 98 and 99 plus 1 which is 100
and 98 over 100 simplifies to 49 over
50. and let's put a box around it so
this simplified is 49 over 50. how
exciting